
[
    {
        "Question": "1+1?",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Incorrect1": "11",
        "Incorrect2": "1",
        "Incorrect3": "111"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is Obamas last name?",
        "Answer": "Obama",
        "Incorrect1": "Wang",
        "Incorrect2": "Sakamata",
        "Incorrect3": "Guichon"
    },
    {
        "Question": "3x3?",
        "Answer": "9",
        "Incorrect1": "3",
        "Incorrect2": "33",
        "Incorrect3": "0"
    },
    {
        "Question": "First month of the year?",
        "Answer": "January",
        "Incorrect1": "February",
        "Incorrect2": "December",
        "Incorrect3": "None of the above"
    },
    {
        "Question": "The answer is 2",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Incorrect1": "3",
        "Incorrect2": "4",
        "Incorrect3": "22"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What does CIT stand for at BCIT?",
        "Answer": "Computer Information Technology",
        "Incorrect1": "Cool Internet Things",
        "Incorrect2": "Cheesy Information Topics",
        "Incorrect3": "Computer Internet Topics"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the powerhouse of the cell?",
        "Answer": "Mitochondria",
        "Incorrect1": "Ribosomes",
        "Incorrect2": "Nucleolus",
        "Incorrect3": "Cytoplasm"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How do you spell Trello",
        "Answer": "Trello",
        "Incorrect1": "Trelbo",
        "Incorrect2": "Elbow",
        "Incorrect3": "Trellaw"
    },
    {
        "Question": "5x5",
        "Answer": "25",
        "Incorrect1": "55",
        "Incorrect2": "5",
        "Incorrect3": "idk lol"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the 6th month of the year?",
        "Answer": "June",
        "Incorrect1": "July",
        "Incorrect2": "May",
        "Incorrect3": "January"
    },
    {
        "Question": "how many bits in a byte?",
        "Answer": "8",
        "Incorrect1": "2",
        "Incorrect2": "4",
        "Incorrect3": "16"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What letter does the word 'Tim' start with?",
        "Answer": "T",
        "Incorrect1": "i",
        "Incorrect2": "m",
        "Incorrect3": "3.14"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What colour represents STOP on traffic lights?",
        "Answer": "Red",
        "Incorrect1": "Green",
        "Incorrect2": "Yellow",
        "Incorrect3": "Purple"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What planet are we on right now?",
        "Answer": "Earth",
        "Incorrect1": "Mars",
        "Incorrect2": "Uranus",
        "Incorrect3": "Venus"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many seconds are in a minute?",
        "Answer": "60",
        "Incorrect1": "100",
        "Incorrect2": "600",
        "Incorrect3": "6"
    }
    ]